<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Choy</title>
    <link>http://www.chrischoy.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chris Choy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 12:29:35 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.chrischoy.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pintos</title>
      <link>http://www.chrischoy.net/projects/pintos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 12:29:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrischoy.net/projects/pintos/</guid>
      <description>#PintOS Pintos is a simple instructional operating system originally designed Ben Ptaff in 2004. For my Operating Systems class project, I worked with my project partner, Ben Weinshel, to implement key OS features that were purposefully absent or poorly implemented in the base version of Pintos.
Part 1: Scheduling and Priority Donation Part 2: System Calls Part 3: Virtual Memory Part 4: File System Management Disclaimer Due to the University of Chicago&amp;rsquo;s Academic Honesty Policy, I may not publicly post any of the code I wrote for this class without my instructor&amp;rsquo;s consent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects Class</title>
      <link>http://www.chrischoy.net/projects-class/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 21:40:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrischoy.net/projects-class/</guid>
      <description>The following are all projects that I have completed as coursework at the University of Chicago. Per the University&amp;rsquo;s Academic policies, I cannot publicly post the code I have written for these projects, nor can I share it privately without my professors&amp;rsquo; explicit consent. If you would like to see the actual code I&amp;rsquo;ve written for these projects, please feel free to reach out to me and I will try to obtain my professors&amp;rsquo; consent!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://www.chrischoy.net/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 17:01:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrischoy.net/resume/</guid>
      <description>Download: [PDF] [ATS-friendly Version] Education University of Chicago | Chicago, IL Bachelor of Science, Computer Science Expected June 2019 Worcester Preparatory School | Berlin, MD High School Diploma, June 2015 Coursework Highlights Operating Systems Computer Architecture Networks and Distributing Systems Statistical Methods and Applications Discrete Mathematics Experience Computer Science Instructional Laboratory, University of Chicago Programmer, Student Office Assistant, Tutor Jan. 2017 - present | Chicago, IL  Utilized Ansible automation in creating and maintaining Mac OS X 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.chrischoy.net/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 02:21:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrischoy.net/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to reach out to me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.chrischoy.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 02:19:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.chrischoy.net/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello World! My name is Christopher Choy. I&amp;rsquo;m a third-year Computer Science major at the University of Chicago.
I consider myself to be a well-rounded individual that can operate well in a variety of environments. I believe my strongest points to be my organization and self-motivation. Previous employers and coworkers have praised my hardworking attitude and amicable nature.
My coursework so far has focused on low-level programming and developing my proficiency in C.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>